[{"answer": "What did they offer", "docId": "Moneyball.txt", "asentId": 3, "question": "What did the that place offer him", "qsentId": 2}, {"answer": "I have. They want more", "docId": "Moneyball.txt", "asentId": 5, "question": "I have. They want more than a little more", "qsentId": 4}, {"answer": "Billy..", "docId": "Moneyball.txt", "asentId": 7, "question": "We just won 102 games with a forty million dollar payroll", "qsentId": 6}, {"answer": "That's not what I asked. I asked can he hit", "docId": "Moneyball.txt", "asentId": 9, "question": "If he's a good hitter, why doesn't he hit good", "qsentId": 8}, {"answer": "my friend was a night security guard at the that place and Beans Factory", "docId": "Moneyball.txt", "asentId": 11, "question": "He's not in baseball. He's in pork and beans", "qsentId": 10}, {"answer": "Hi", "docId": "Moneyball.txt", "asentId": 13, "question": "My name is my friend", "qsentId": 12}, {"answer": "Why does my friend listen to you", "docId": "Moneyball.txt", "asentId": 15, "question": "He just did", "qsentId": 14}, {"answer": "Really", "docId": "Moneyball.txt", "asentId": 17, "question": "Who are you", "qsentId": 16}, {"answer": "I'm not sure what you're asking me", "docId": "Moneyball.txt", "asentId": 19, "question": "Huh? Oh my friend? I told him I like my friend", "qsentId": 18}, {"answer": "Where did you go to school", "docId": "Moneyball.txt", "asentId": 21, "question": "I hate that place", "qsentId": 20}, {"answer": "Look for an inefficiencies in statistics", "docId": "Moneyball.txt", "asentId": 23, "question": "Exploit the fact that unspectacular runs are just as valuable as 45", "qsentId": 22}, {"answer": "Examine the ways that runs are scored and prevented", "docId": "Moneyball.txt", "asentId": 25, "question": "Unspectacular runs are more valuable", "qsentId": 24}, {"answer": "Math isn't a theory", "docId": "Moneyball.txt", "asentId": 27, "question": "It's right", "qsentId": 26}, {"answer": "If it's righ", "docId": "Moneyball.txt", "asentId": 29, "question": "It sounds right", "qsentId": 28}, {"answer": "It's right", "docId": "Moneyball.txt", "asentId": 31, "question": "It is right", "qsentId": 30}, {"answer": "It is right", "docId": "Moneyball.txt", "asentId": 33, "question": "It isn't", "qsentId": 32}, {"answer": "Hey, Art", "docId": "Moneyball.txt", "asentId": 35, "question": "I got a lot to do", "qsentId": 34}, {"answer": "No I can't", "docId": "Moneyball.txt", "asentId": 37, "question": "How about you deal with the manager's contract and then put a team on the field", "qsentId": 36}, {"answer": " Yep", "docId": "Moneyball.txt", "asentId": 39, "question": "Fuck", "qsentId": 38}, {"answer": "You got good", "docId": "Moneyball.txt", "asentId": 41, "question": "That's... that's not the way most 12 year olds play", "qsentId": 40}, {"answer": "You don't go on the road with the team", "docId": "Moneyball.txt", "asentId": 43, "question": "Why don't you", "qsentId": 42}, {"answer": "Fine. my friend, would you have a seat for a moment, I need to talk to you", "docId": "Moneyball.txt", "asentId": 45, "question": "I was pretending you weren't sitting", "qsentId": 44}, {"answer": "Really? Why", "docId": "Moneyball.txt", "asentId": 47, "question": "Why wouldn't you want people to notice you", "qsentId": 46}, {"answer": "Well, I guess you could sneak up on people. Or eavesdrop on their conversations. You could be a spy.  So how's school", "docId": "Moneyball.txt", "asentId": 49, "question": "What kind of teacher doesn't let you ask questions", "qsentId": 48}, {"answer": "I know, it's terrible. Look, I promise I'll quit in November if you promise not to worry about it", "docId": "Moneyball.txt", "asentId": 51, "question": "Pinkie swear", "qsentId": 50}, {"answer": "Okay. my friend's Blackberry chimes. He ignores it", "docId": "Moneyball.txt", "asentId": 53, "question": " You feel like what", "qsentId": 52}, {"answer": "Why do you do it", "docId": "Moneyball.txt", "asentId": 55, "question": "How do you do it? Every ball park's different", "qsentId": 54}, {"answer": "my friend", "docId": "Moneyball.txt", "asentId": 57, "question": "You remember my friend", "qsentId": 56}, {"answer": "It's just one game", "docId": "Moneyball.txt", "asentId": 59, "question": "The point is always tomorrow's game", "qsentId": 58}, {"answer": "That's the point, you think", "docId": "Moneyball.txt", "asentId": 61, "question": "No, the point", "qsentId": 60}, {"answer": " Sometimes you have to shake it up.  my friend, Pea's going on the blocks, you're my first call... because he's making the rest of the team look bad... He's going to be rookie of the year..", "docId": "Moneyball.txt", "asentId": 63, "question": "He's an all star my friend...", "qsentId": 62}, {"answer": "I don't want to go 15 rounds, my friend, the lin", "docId": "Moneyball.txt", "asentId": 65, "question": "I am starting my friend at first", "qsentId": 64}, {"answer": "I don't think so, he plays for the that place now", "docId": "Moneyball.txt", "asentId": 67, "question": "Along with German, my friend and my friend", "qsentId": 66}, {"answer": "Every starter, we want to see 100 pitches by the 5th inning", "docId": "Moneyball.txt", "asentId": 69, "question": "Yeah. I mean, my friend drained 38 pitches", "qsentId": 68}, {"answer": "Nah, make it Mr. my friend", "docId": "Moneyball.txt", "asentId": 71, "question": "I'm screwin' with you, my friend", "qsentId": 70}, {"answer": "That's what I do. That's what you pay me to do", "docId": "Moneyball.txt", "asentId": 73, "question": "I don't get thrown out much", "qsentId": 72}, {"answer": "Excuse me", "docId": "Moneyball.txt", "asentId": 75, "question": "You've never seen a that place who was a player", "qsentId": 74}, {"answer": "You're special", "docId": "Moneyball.txt", "asentId": 77, "question": "As a matter of fact I'm not paying you 7 million bucks, my friend. The that place are paying half your salary. That's what the New York that place think of you.", "qsentId": 76}, {"answer": "Yeah", "docId": "Moneyball.txt", "asentId": 79, "question": "Head problems", "qsentId": 78}, {"answer": "If we have a lead late in the game and they have runners on base, I'd rather not see my friend out of the bullpen", "docId": "Moneyball.txt", "asentId": 81, "question": "That's what you should do. Baseball's a game of situations and you should make the decision when the time comes. Except you should make it now", "qsentId": 80}, {"answer": "Twent", "docId": "Moneyball.txt", "asentId": 83, "question": "my friend?  No", "qsentId": 82}, {"answer": "my friend says he needs two hundred and twent", "docId": "Moneyball.txt", "asentId": 85, "question": "my friend says he'll pay for my friend himself, sell him next year, and keep the profit", "qsentId": 84}, {"answer": "I pitch tonight", "docId": "Moneyball.txt", "asentId": 87, "question": "I no wanna pitch tonight", "qsentId": 86}, {"answer": "No, honey. Absolutely not. And even if I did, I'm not going anywhere. I told you not to worry about me. People say a lot of crazy things and they don't always know what they're talking about. It's just gossip. Like gossipers at school", "docId": "Moneyball.txt", "asentId": 89, "question": "And once you do find out who the authorities are, ignore them at all costs", "qsentId": 88}, {"answer": "Everything's fine, honey. I'm not going anywhere. The only way I would lose my job is if someone was to give me a better one. Don't worry about me, okay? Dad knows what he's doing", "docId": "Moneyball.txt", "asentId": 91, "question": "Pinkie swear", "qsentId": 90}, {"answer": "Hey, my friend. What's on your mind", "docId": "Moneyball.txt", "asentId": 93, "question": "16.5 actually. But as a hitter, you will create 70 runs. 70 runs wins us an awful lot of ball games. I can live with that. Can you live with that", "qsentId": 92}, {"answer": "that place", "docId": "Moneyball.txt", "asentId": 95, "question": "See what the city's about", "qsentId": 94}, {"answer": "I don't know. Depends on if we beat you today. Probably celebrating.  So my that place says I gotta be more social. What was your name", "docId": "Moneyball.txt", "asentId": 97, "question": "I'm my friend", "qsentId": 96}, {"answer": "And Cash. And a player to be named later", "docId": "Moneyball.txt", "asentId": 99, "question": "I don't want your job", "qsentId": 98}, {"answer": "Did he make you a good offer", "docId": "Moneyball.txt", "asentId": 101, "question": "What was it", "qsentId": 100}, {"answer": "I don't know. I've never heard you say you did", "docId": "Moneyball.txt", "asentId": 103, "question": "You're not doing it for the money", "qsentId": 102}, {"answer": " It was a metap", "docId": "Moneyball.txt", "asentId": 105, "question": "That was a hell of a baseball season, boss", "qsentId": 104}]